ILGWU Photographs 5780 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 1 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 13)
  includes: Group photo including David Dubinsky, Potofsky, LBJ, Meany; LBJ speech to ILG members; Robert Kennedy and LBJ at an ILGWU function, David Dubinsky present; Speech by Johnson to crowd of ILGWU members; David Dubinsky and LBJ at rally; ILGWU members demonstrating with placards for LBJ; Large poster advertising Kennedy and LBJ in 1962 in ILGWU Hall; Johnson and David Dubinsky in White House, Jan. 21, 1964; LBJ being pinned at convention, Antonini in background; Local 552 "Union Women" demonstration supporting LBJ; LBJ and wife at White House with David Dubinsky; Italian Dressmakers Local 89 parade float in support of the LBJ Hubert H. Humphrey presidential ticket; Garment Center Rally for Johnson, Humphrey and Kennedy in New York City, Crowd scenes; LBJ sitting with Mayor Wagner; Shop scene with David Dubinsky and LBJ - David Dubinsky showing LBJ how to cut a garment; 1960 Campaign for Kennedy - LBJ in Allentown, PA; LBJ shaking hands with people; Portrait of LBJ; LBJ in factory checking out coats; LBJ with Harry S. Truman at his side, signed the Medicare Bill into Law, Lady Bird Johnson, Vice President Hubert Humphrey, and former First Lady Bess Truman looking on, August 15, 1965; Crowd awaiting LBJ's speech; LBJ at Lincoln Memorial in a Tribute on Lincoln's birthday; Louis Stulberg and David Dubinsky escorting Mrs. Johnson around a plant; LBJ shaking hands with Upton Sinclair (author of The Jungle), at a Bill signing to increase regulations on meat packing; LBJ meeting with George Meany; LBJ, David Dubinsky, Mayor Wagner walking the streets of New York City; LBJ and David Dubinsky at ceremony celebrating the 50th Anniversary of the ILGWU Health Center. (folder 23 includes Frances Perkins? On stage with LBJ?)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 2 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 3 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 4 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 5 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 6 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 7 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 8 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 9 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 10 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 11 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 12 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 13 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 1) [folder 14 of 14] (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. [folder 1 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 1)
  includes: Rallies for LBJ and HHH by ILGWU members; Johnson speech, present are: Robert F. Kennedy, Lady Bird Johnson, David Dubinsky, Adlai Stevenson, and Mayor Robert Wagner; David Dubinsky speech with LBJ next to him; Photograph signed by LBJ with a message for David Dubinsky; crowd and demonstration scenes in support of LBJ campaign; David Dubinsky shaking hands with Lady Bird Johnson at the White House; Shop scene with LBJ and David Dubinsky at cutters; LBJ and Robert Kennedy at Rally; 1969, David Dubinsky holding his Presidential Medal of Freedom
- Johnson, Lyndon B. [folder 2 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. [folder 3 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. [folder 4 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Johnson, Lyndon B. [folder 5 of 5] (Box 16, Folder 5)
- Kennedy, John F. - selected (see also: Bx. 50 ff 2) [folder 1 of 3] (Box 16, Folder 6)
  includes: JFK speech in front of CO-OP project; JFK standing with David Dubinsky in front of CO-OP building; Chaikin and Kennedy in Kennedy's office; David Dubinsky, Mayor Wagner and JFK at CO-OP ceremony; David Dubinsky, JFK and Antonini speaking; Women show their support for JFK; Demonstration in support of JFK; Potofsky, Meany, David Dubinsky, JFK at White House with others; Portrait of JFK; Photo of Kennedy at AFL- CIO, November 15, 1963
- Kennedy, John F. - selected (see also: Bx. 50 ff 2) [folder 2 of 3] (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Kennedy, John F. - selected (see also: Bx. 50 ff 2) [folder 3 of 3] (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 1 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 9)
  includes: Demonstration and rally photos; Crowd scenes; Demonstrations with placards by ILGWU members supporting JFK; CFK at CO-OP ceremony with David Dubinsky; Contact sheets of Kennedy rallies; JFK Speech; Portrait of JFK; JFK, Secretary of Labor Arthur Goldberg and George Meany at Kennedy's home; Kennedy motorcades in Pennsylvania; JFK with Sol C. Chaikin; JFK with Francis Leahey; Kennedy in shop scene; Men and women wearing Kennedy buttons and hats; Senator Herbert Lehman and JFK in a campaign strategy meeting; JFK at White House desk; David Dubinsky speech at JFK - LBJ rally; photos from Eleanor Roosevelt's Funeral
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 2 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 3 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 4 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 5 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 6 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 7 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 8 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 9 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 10 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Kennedy, John F. (see also: Bx. 50 ff 3) [folder 11 of 11] (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Kennedy, Robert and D. Dubinsky - selected (Box 17, Folder 1)
  includes: Speech by Robert Kennedy; RFK, Jacob Javits and David Dubinsky speaking; David Dubinsky, RFK, Stulberg in a group photo; RFK speech to the American Jewish Committee
- Kennedy, Robert and D. Dubinsky (see also: Bx. 50 ff 4) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  includes: RFK, David Dubinsky and Jacob Javits speaking; David Dubinsky Holding up RFK's hand, September 14, 1964; Speech by RFK; David Dubinsky addressing audience in Union Hall; Individual shot of RFK; RFK shaking hands with Mayor Wagner, David Dubinsky present; Humphrey, RFK and David Dubinsky on podium; Demonstration in support for RFK
- Kennedy, Edward - selected (Box 17, Folder 3)
  includes: Group photos Chaikin and wife, Ted Kennedy, others; Ted Kennedy speaking; Ted Kennedy with official
- Kennedy, Edward (Box 17, Folder 4)
  includes: Group photos - Ted Kennedy "centerspread"; Ted Kennedy at some type of small gathering (may be a funeral) (in color)
- King, Jr. Dr. Martin Luther [empty folder] (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Koch, Edward - selected (Box 17, Folder 6)
  includes: Sol Chaikin and Mayor Ed Koch in City Hall (NYC), holding a Proclamation that May is Cambodian Relief Month
- Koch, Edward (Box 17, Folder 7)
  includes: Chaikin and Koch at City Hall (NYC) holding a proclamation that May is Cambodian Relief Month; Koch at banquet with Chaikin
- Kramer, Philip - selected (Box 17, Folder 8)
  includes: Group photo - Arthur Marcus, Jay Fialkow, Mr. and Mrs. Philip Kramer, Sol Chaikin, Selma Gottlieb, and Edward Milano at a ceremony Honoring Philip Kramer
- Labor Day - selected (Box 17, Folder 9)
  includes: Parade photos; ILG members march with placards stating ILGWU contract victories and the years they won them; ILGWU Fire Wardens Fire Truck; Locals 23, 99, 62 marching; Mayor Wagner, David Dubinsky observing the 1959 Labor Day parade; Local 25 marching in 1960 parade, with placards promoting Civil Rights; David Dubinsky, Wagner, Meany (Grand Marshal) observing parade; ILGWU Labor Day float, advertising the 'style of the day' and promoting the Union Label
- Labor Day [folder 1 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 10)
  includes: Parade participants getting ready to march with their signs; Union Made products display; Float promoting ILGWU accomplishments - CO-OP Housing project, Unity House and the ILGWU Health Center; Float with ILGWU Union Label and 'Our Record", listing contract accomplishments; Local 105, 10, 91, 40, 62, 89, 155 marching; ILGWU workers watching the parade; Parade with Empire State Building in background; 1960 Parade - Mayor Wagner, David Dubinsky and Grand Marshal George Meany; ILGWU Fare Warden Fire Truck; Local 499 (in Herrin, Illinois); Meany and Stulberg getting ready to march; Local 99 marching with placards: "More Schools, More Teachers" and "We Are ONE Union Family...All Races, Creeds, and Colors"; Local 122 marching in Atlanta Labor Day Parade
- Labor Day [folder 2 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Labor Day [folder 3 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Labor Day [folder 4 of 4] (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Labor Day Parade, 1959 - selected (Box 17, Folder 14)
  includes: 1959 Labor Day Parade Viewing Stand - Mayor Wagner, David Dubinsky, Nelson Rockefeller
- Labor Day Parade, 1959 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 15)
  includes: Parade in front of the New York Public Library (Fifth Ave and 42nd Street, New York City); with placards supporting the "Forand Bill"; Locals 155, 48, 40, 98, 9, 57, 77, 107 marching; Individual photo of Grand Marshal Harry Van Arsdale; ILGWU Parade float; Antonini marching; people blowing up balloons; individual face shots of Antonini and other members
- Labor Day Parade, 1959 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Labor Day Parade, 1960 - selected (Box 17, Folder 17)
  includes: Local 89 Parade Float; head of the ILGWU Parade delegation in front of the New York Public Library (5th Avenue and 42nd Street, New York City); two girls in dresses with the ILGWU "Union Label" carrying balloons; Antonini, David Dubinsky, and Zimmerman walking together in parade
- Labor Day Parade, 1960 [folder 1 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 18)
  includes: Parade procession on 5th Avenue, New York City; New York City Central Labor Council; ILGWU members watching the parade; David Dubinsky handing Mayor Wagner packs of matches with the Union Label; David Dubinsky watching parade; David Dubinsky, Antonini and Zimmerman walking in parade; Mayor Wagner and David Dubinsky in Parade observation deck of parade; Local 10 delegation marching with yard sticks in hand; Local 20 member wearing an ILGWU armband
- Labor Day Parade, 1960 [folder 2 of 2] (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Labor Stage - selected (Box 17, Folder 20)
  includes: Photo of Labor Stage Building
- Labor Stage (Box 17, Folder 21)
  includes: performances at the Labor Stage
- LaGuardia - selected (Box 17, Folder 22)
  includes: Antonini shaking hands with LaGuardia; Shop scene - LaGuardia watching button hole maker working; Speech by David Dubinsky pointing to portrait of LaGuardia; David Dubinsky at podium with LaGuardia
- LaGuardia (Box 17, Folder 23)
  includes: David Dubinsky and LaGuardia at art show; LaGuardia speech to Local 22; Antonini about to shake hands with LaGuardia, also on podium David Dubinsky; speech by David Dubinsky; Sam Shore, manager for Local 62, at LaGuardia's office to sign an agreement, October 13, 1937; Banquet scene - David Dubinsky speech; October 12, 1937, Columbus Day celebration at Hippodrome - Governor, Mayor, Antonini, Judge Poletti; LaGuardia signing agreement between dress union officials and manufacturers - present are: Schlesinger, Hochman, David Dubinsky, LaGuardia, Herman Florsheimer and Nat Borishin
- Lazar, Robert (Box 17, Folder 23a)
- League for Industrial Democracy - selected (Box 17, Folder 24)
  includes: Luncheon, 1949, David Dubinsky is guest of honor; banquet scene including Ralph Wright, David Dubinsky, A.S. Hayes, William Green, Dr. Ralph Bunche; David Dubinsky, Senator Lehman, and Nagler; David Dubinsky on dais with George Meany
- Legislation - Taft Hartley, Minimum Wage - selected (Box 17, Folder 25)
  includes: David Dubinsky testifying; Speech by David Dubinsky at Taft - Hartley Protest Rally, present William Green, Mayor O'Dwyer, Meany, Antonini, Madison Square Garden, 1947 (backdrop - slogan "Mr. President: Veto the Hartley - Taft Slave Labor Bill"); David Dubinsky shaking hands with Mayor O'Dwyer, William green present; Meeting with New York members of the House of Representatives: Dr. Lazare Teper, Rep. Frank Horton, Mayor Stephen May (Rochester), Potofsky, and Rep. Emanuel Celler; David Dubinsky testifying at Minimum Wage Hearings
- Legislation - Taft Hartley, Minimum Wage (Box 18, Folder 1)
  includes: Speech by David Dubinsky at Taft Hartley Protest Rally, Madison Square Garden, 1947, also present are William Green, Mayor O'Dwyer, Meany, Antonini (backdrop - slogan "Mr. President: Veto the Hartley - Taft Slave Labor Bill"); Chaikin testifying; David Dubinsky testifying at Minimum Wage hearings
- Lehman, Herbert - selected (Box 18, Folder 2)
  includes: group photo at dinner honoring Governor Lehman, Jan. 31, 1943, includes David Dubinsky, Lehman, Potofsky; David Dubinsky talking informally with Governor Lehman; Speech by Gov. Lehman; Lehman, David Dubinsky and Meany speaking
- Lehman, Herbert (Box 18, Folder 3)
  includes: Lehman, David Dubinsky and Meany talking; Governor and Mrs. Lehman at 80th Birthday Celebration; Lehman shaking hands with Isidore Nagler, David Dubinsky present, Speech by Lehman; Portrait of Lehman
- Lemlich, Clara (Box 18, Folder 3a)
  includes: Lemlich in a group photo (a), individual portrait, detail from group photo (b)
- Lewis, John L. - selected (Box 18, Folder 4)
  includes: Lewis and David Dubinsky talking; Lewis and David Dubinsky sitting on platform
- Lewis, John L. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  includes: Lewis, David Dubinsky and William Green at Banquet; Lewis and David Dubinsky shaking hands; Lewis on Atlantic City (NJ) Boardwalk
- Liberal Party - selected [folder 1 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 6)
  includes: Group photo - black boys and girls pose around a sign for people to get out and vote; Liberal Party poster in a shop scene where three workers talk about the upcoming election; Photo of a delivery truck with sign "Forward with Roosevelt"; Demonstrations with Placards advocating higher rent controls; Liberal Party Rally - large sign "Herbert Lehman, Walter Lynch, Ferdinand Pecora"; Nagler, Lehman, Morris and David Dubinsky at luncheon honoring Nagler and his 30 years of service; Sign strung across 7th Ave. (New York City) in support of FDR for President, Henry Wallace for Vice President, and James Mead for U.S. Senator; Assemblyman Irwin Steivyut and Nathaniel Minkoff shaking hands; Sidney Hillman, Antonini working; Reelection campaign for LaGuardia; Employees for Roosevelt preparing to campaign on the street with placards; Local 135 (Newark, NJ) demonstration with placards - 'Repeal Hartley - Taft Act', 'Fair Tax Elect Stevenson'; man sweeping broken glass in storefront window of what appears to be a campaign headquarters that was broken by a thrown chair; demonstration for Stevenson - Kefauver - Stevenson riding in car, receiving flowers; Harry S Truman looking over a campaign poster with David Dubinsky; FDR about to speak, David Dubinsky next to him; David Dubinsky, Lehman, Eleanor Roosevelt, John Childs, Pearl Willen, and George S. Counts in group photo; Painting with placards advocating many Union platforms: 5 day week, right to organize, shorter hours, collective bargaining, abolition of child labor, higher wages and Social Security; Local 135 showing support for Stevenson with posters; Supporters demonstrate with placards for Lehman for Senator; rally to get people to register to vote
- Liberal Party - selected [folder 2 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Liberal Party - selected [folder 3 of 3] (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Liberal Party [folder 1 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 9)
  includes: Shop scene with poster advocating the Roosevelt - Lehman ticket; Rally for Mayor Wagner's reelection; Local 10 meeting supporting Lehman; David Dubinsky speech; Antonini speech; Jack Rubenstein, Local 35 member bloodied; ILGWU members registering for 1 year army draft at local public schools; Newbold Morris keynote address (press conference) at Hotel Astor (headquarters), September 9, 1949; Manhattan Center - Joseph O'Leary, Walter Lynch, David Dubinsky, October 5, 1950; Tickertape parade for President Truman; speech by David Dubinsky; Local 102 hanging political posters on garment trucks; Dress Liberal Party Club, Guest speaker Eleanor Roosevelt, September 25, 1956; 13 year old volunteer Billy Page sings his own songs on sound truck touring the garment district; Local 62 campaigning on Madison Ave.; Photo of the voting booth ballot; FDR shaking hands with Pecora; Joe Kessler and Newbold Morris at the Hotel Diplomat, November 3, 1941; Local 22 in Manhattan Center; Liberal Party candidates Juvenal Marchisio, Rudolph Halley, and Chase Mellen Jr.; Local 105 at Headquarters, October 26, 1951; Local 60 meeting for Halley, October 12, 1953; Speech by Lehman; David Dubinsky speech at ILG Studio, October 16, 1953; FDR, Rose, Childs and Stulberg (speech); Garment Center Rally for FDR Jr. and Harriman, October 5, 1954, David Dubinsky, Stulberg on dais; rally shot; signing of nomination petition; FDR Jr. and Manager of Local 66 Zachary Freedman shaking hands; FDR Jr. speech to Local 66 members; AA Berle, Chairman of the Liberal Party; Ben Davidson speech; Dais for Liberal Party convention: Charles Zimmerman, Alex Rose, Louis Stulberg, David Dubinsky, Antonini, and Rabbi Edward Klein; Speech by Robert Kennedy to Liberal Party; Political sign sponsored by the Butchers Union Local 234, supporting Lehman for Governor, O'Dwyer for Mayor; Zimmerman introducing Harriman to workers at Max Weisensons Inc.; Ferdinand Pecora speech to noon time New York City Streetwalkers; Samuel Otto - VP and Pacific Coast Director, and Isidore Stenzor holding signs made in preparation for Adlai Stevenson's welcoming to Los Angeles; Newbold Morris Speech; New York City parade welcoming President Truman to Garment District; David Dubinsky speaking to conference table full of people; Isidore Sorkin speech to Local 38 members promoting Halley, October 14, 1953; FDR Jr. speech to Local 91; Liberal Party Rally - posters for Wagner, Stevenson, Kefauver; Harriman accepting nomination for Liberal Party for Governor; Two women holding a campaign poster from the Liberal Party Harriman for Governor, De Leca for Lieutenant Governor, Roosevelt for Attorney General, and Levitt for Controller; Parade marching to City Hall to meet Adlai Stevenson; David Dubinsky addressing crowd from sound truck, Lehman standing right next to him; Photo of Liberal Party Leaders: Alfange, O'Leary, David Dubinsky, Uviller, and Rose
- Liberal Party [folder 2 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Liberal Party [folder 3 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Liberal Party [folder 4 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Liberal Party [folder 5 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Liberal Party [folder 6 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Liberal Party [folder 7 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Liberal Party [folder 8 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Liberal Party [folder 9 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Liberal Party [folder 10 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Liberal Party [folder 11 of 11] (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Liberal Party [folder 1 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 1)
  includes: Liberal party rally and speeches supporting the candidates; Posters of the Ballot, telling people to vote "Line C"; Rose, David Dubinsky and Hayes sitting and talking; Banquet shot - David Dubinsky, Stulberg and Meany; Eleanor Roosevelt with David Dubinsky; Harry S. Truman pointing to a campaign poster advocating that voting is being a "Front Line Citizen"; FDR Jr. officially accepting his Nomination and Liberal Party Support; other convention and campaign photos
- Liberal Party [folder 2 of 2] (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Lindsay, John - selected (Box 19, Folder 3)
  includes: Lindsay talking to David Dubinsky; Lindsay presenting David Dubinsky with the Diamond Jubilee medal; Harry Van Arsdale Jr. shaking hands with John Lindsay, David Dubinsky present; Liberal Party candidates meet - Donald Harrington, David Dubinsky, Timothy Costello, John Lindsay, and Alex Rose; Speech by Lindsay at Liberal Party Dinner, October 8, 1969
- Lindsay, John (Box 19, Folder 4)
  includes: Shop Scene - Lindsay observing garment workers and talking to them; Speech by Lindsay at the Liberal Party Dinner, October 8, 1959; David Dubinsky and Arlene Francis at Lindsay Rally from his 1966 Campaign; Lindsay speaking from a Sound truck, David Dubinsky next to him; Lindsay shaking hands with Stulberg; at the International Rescue Committee dinner honoring David Dubinsky, Americana Hotel, December 13, 1966, Francis Cardinal Spellman and John Lindsay
- Living and Working Conditions (sketches) (Box 19, Folder 5)
  includes: political sketches - "The Squatters of New York City"; "Underground Lodgings for the Poor, Greenwich Street, New York City"; Monopolist viewing Immigrant (Pauper) labor as more valuable than American Workingmen (on strike)
- Locals and Joint Boards - selected (Box 19, Folder 6)
  includes: Celia Kaufman, Delegate to convention circa 1912; American Lady Corset Makers, Local 318 on Strike with placards picketing; Installation of Local 117, Manhattan Opera House, David Dubinsky and Antonini present; Installation of Local 60, Webster Hall; Local 62 picketing with Placards in front of Rembrandt; Penna. Interstate Convention of the Cotton Dress & Misc. Trades Dept., 1/20/38, Locals 109-131 - 209; Picketers from the American Lady Corset Company talking to passersby and police; Group Photo - David Dubinsky, Antonini, Hochman, Zimmerman; Installation of the Belt makers Union; Conference in San Antonio to organize a local, David Dubinsky and Regional Manager Perlstein, June, 1935; Angry Local 132 members who were arrested for union activities demonstrate with placards for David Dubinsky to remove Manager Martin Feldman from his office
- Locals and Joint Boards (See also map case) [folder 1 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 7)
  includes: Wilbur Daniels speaking before installation ceremony; Speech by Edward Schneider of the Children's Dressmakers Local 91; Signing of the Local 62 Agreement; Stulberg, David Dubinsky, Bialis and Antonini in Banquet scene; Group Photo - Local 22, 66 ILGWU Retiree Club; Manager Schoenwald posing with a group of Retired members at a recent Rally, sponsored by the New York City Central Labor Council in protest of budget cuts; Speech by David Dubinsky to workers at Mode O'Day Corporation, celebrating the installation of a new Los Angeles local, Rose Pesotta present, #384; David Dubinsky addressing the Los Angeles Dress and Cloak Board, present are Isidore Stenzor, Hyman D. Langer, and Louis Levy; Local 339 Banquet in honor of David Dubinsky, Miami, Florida, January 4, 1949; Installation if Local 217, Trenton, New Jersey; Man with an official ballot voting; Manager Jack Hochman and Charles Zimmerman congratulate first Executive Board of Local 159 Dress Industry Office Employees; ILGWU parade float on the streets of Toronto; Local 142 artificial flower makers demonstrating with placards it advertise Union Label artificial flowers; 1912 convention, 1949 Rally at Roosevelt Auditorium; Long Island Locals 57, 77 set up relief effort for the Sioux Indians of North & South Dakota - collecting canned food to send; 25th Anniversary of Locals 1, 3, and 17 merger; Group Photo - Convention Delegates Dressmakers Union Local 22, 50th Golden Jubilee Convention, Atlantic City, New Jersey
- Locals and Joint Boards (See also map case) [folder 2 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Locals and Joint Boards (See also map case) [folder 3 of 3] (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Local 9 (Box 19, Folder 10)